<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<banner>
	<globals
		width="496" height="375" 
		currentItem="0" radius="0"
		showButtons="true"
		showPlayPauseButton="true" showContent="true"
		bgColor="#000000" bgAlpha="0.8" bgPaddingBottom="0"
		titleColor="#FFFFFF" titleFontSize="16"
		descriptionColor="#999999" descriptionFontSize="11"
		cssFile="assets/css/banner.css"
	/>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/01TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/01.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Gutierrez smokes a cigarette in her home in Tempe, Ariz. A devout Catholic, Gutierrez  sees the Virgin as an important part of her faith.]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/02TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/02.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Gutierrez smokes a cigarette in her home in Tempe, Ariz. A devout Catholic, Gutierrez considers the Virgin an important part of her faith.]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/03TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/03.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Raquel Gutierrez pulls out an image of the Virgin of Guadalupe in her home Tuesday morning in Tempe, Ariz. Gutierrez, a devout Catholic, has a strong devotion to the Virgin of Guadalupe which she has passed onto her four daughters although only one remains Catholic today. Photo by Deanna Dent]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/04TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/04.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Gutierrez's grandson plays with her dog in the living room. She says she has tried to pass on her religious convictions to her children and grandchildren.]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/05TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/05.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Raquel Gutierrez keeps a Virgin of Guadalupe outside her home Tuesday morning in Tempe, Ariz. Gutierrez, a devout Catholic, has a strong devotion to the Virgin of Guadalupe which she has passed onto her four daughters although only one remains Catholic today. Photo by Deanna Dent]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/06TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/06.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Raquel Gutierrez has a mural of the Virgin of Guadalupe in her kitchen in her home in Tempe, Ariz. Gutierrez, a devout Catholic, has a strong devotion to the Virgin of Guadalupe which she has passed onto her four daughters although only one remains Catholic today. Photo by Deanna Dent]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/07TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/07.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Raquel Gutierrez shares an earring of the Virgin of Guadalupe Tuesday morning in Tempe, Ariz. Gutierrez, a devout Catholic, has a strong devotion to the Virgin of Guadalupe which she has passed onto her four daughters although only one remains Catholic today. Photo by Deanna Dent ]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/08TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/08.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Raquel Gutierrez relaxes inside her home Tuesday morning in Tempe, Ariz. Gutierrez, a devout Catholic, has a strong devotion to the Virgin of Guadalupe which she has passed onto her four daughters although only one remains Catholic today. Photo by Deanna Dent]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>assets/nodes/3d1a/09TB.jpg</thumbnail>
		<image>assets/nodes/3d1a/09.jpg</image>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Raquel Gutierrez's Virgin of Guadalupe that was given to her by a Catholic priest in Sells, Arizona. Gutierrez, a devout Catholic, has a strong devotion to the Virgin of Guadalupe which she has passed onto her four daughters although only one remains Catholic today. Photo by Deanna Dent]]></description>
		<timer>5</timer>
	</item>
</banner>